# Rachel L Deckard

4081 Meander Bend Apt 3B, Indianapolis, IN 46268 | (317) 590-1065 | rachelleedeckard@gmail.com

### **Summary**

Dedicated and driven individual with an extensive history in customer service and sales. Student at Eleven Fifty Academy for Microsoft .NET Course. Many years of experience in multiple leadership and management roles. Currently seeking new career opportunities in the technology space.

## **Core Competencies**

- Microsoft Office
- G Suite
- Salesforce
- C#
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

- HTML
- Git
- GitHub
- Unit Testing
- Visual Studio

#### **Education**

Eleven Fifty Academy	Fishers, IN
Microsoft .NET	July 2019 – December 2019
Aveda Fredric's Institute	Indianapolis, IN
Esthetics Honors	Graduated August 2018

# **Experience**

- Manage check in and check out window and input patient's demographics into EMR.
- Check insurance eligibility and accept payments, including balancing batch at end of day.
- Maintain patient files and paperwork, file charts, and pull charts for next day.

Responsibilities

- Day to day operations including opening, closing, shipment, and assisting customers.
- Being an essential resource for local salons and spas.
- Informing clients of the latest brands and tools to help them build their business.
- Promote classes for continuing education

Makeup Advisor	Indianapolis, IN August 2018 to August 2019
<ul> <li>Responsibilities</li> <li>Perform both walk-in and appointment makeovers.</li> <li>Assist clients with finding the makeup routine that best suited organize and promote in store events both within own brace.</li> <li>Keep up to date client book that allows for consistent and maintain personal and division goals and metrics through email, phone, test, and written thank you notes.</li> </ul>	nd and throughout store. reliable sales.
Assistant Store Manager	Indianapolis, IN
Talbots	May 2015 to October 2017
Responsibilities	
<ul> <li>Helping women look and feel her best.</li> </ul>	
<ul> <li>Handling everyday operational activities and store product</li> </ul>	tivity.
<ul> <li>Coaching team about individual growth and assisting them</li> </ul>	with their client books and client relationship.
<ul> <li>Maintaining and executing any visual merchandising.</li> </ul>	
Acting Store Manager	Indianapolis, IN
Talbots	September 2016 to February 2017
Responsibilities	
<ul> <li>Developing a strong team that provides our guest with a ur</li> </ul>	nique, personal experience.
<ul> <li>Creating schedule and maintaining payroll every month as</li> </ul>	
<ul> <li>Leading the team to success through listening, inquiring, a</li> </ul>	

Coach December 2012 to May 2015

Responsibilities

- Providing a luxury experience for customers in everyday engagements.
- Reaching and exceeding personal and store sales goals through an independent and strong work ethic.
- Maintaining an up to date client book and growing relationships with customers through phone and email.

#### **Certificates and Licenses**

Eleven Fifty Academy August 2019 .NET Gold Badge

Indiana Professional Licensing Board August 2018 – September 2022 Esthetics License

# **References**

Available Upon Request